John M. Webster fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
John M. Webster fonds
1962 - 2006
F-222
3.26 m of textual records
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
Webster, John M.
Professor John M. Webster is a scientist in the field of nematology. He was a Professor of Biological Sciences at SFU from 1971 to 2001. He remains a Professor Emeritus at SFU.
Professor Webster was born in Wakefield, England on 5 May 1936. He married Carolyn Ann McGillivray in 1970 and they have two children, Gordon John and Sandra Jane. He also has 3 grandchildren.
Webster became interested in biology through the influence of his high school biology teacher who eventually recommended the University of London (Imperial College) for its biology program. While at Imperial College, he focused on parasitology after attending a lecture by the Professor of Parasitology. Eventually, scholarship funding for a PhD in nematology became available and he took it. Webster received a B.Sc. in Zoology with special honours in Parasitology in 1958 and a Ph.D. DIC (Diploma of the Imperial College) in Plant Nematology from the same institution in 1962. Since then he has also received a Senior University Administrator's Diploma from the University of Western Ontario and a D.Sc. in Zoology-Nematology from the University of London, England.
From 1958 to 1961 Webster was a Agricultural Research Scholar at the University of London (Imperial College) and from 1961 to 1966 he was a Scientific Officer at Rothamsted Experimental Station in England, one of the top research stations in Europe at the time. He then moved to Canada where he was a research scientist at the Agriculture Canada Biological Control Research Institute in Belleville, Ontario from 1966-1967.
In 1967, he made the move to university life by accepting the position of Associate Professor in the Department of Biological Sciences at the newly-formed SFU. He became a full professor in 1971. During his time at SFU Professor Webster held a number of administrative positions including: Dean of Graduate Studies Pro-Tem, 1970-1971; Chair of Biological Sciences, 1974-1976; Dean of Science 1976-1980; Associate Vice-President, Academic, 1980-1985; Associate Vice-President & Dean of Graduate Studies, 1982-1985; University Research Professor, 1987-1988. In 2001 he became Professor Emeritus.
In addition to his research and administrative work at SFU, Webster has also been involved with a number of government related organizations, such as on the executive of the Science Council of Canada, member of the Premiers Advisory Council on Science & Technology, Chair of the Life Sciences Committee of the Natural Sciences and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC), member and Chairman of the Board of TRIUMF, member of Council and President of the Western Canadian Universities Marine Biological Society, and the President of the Canadian Academy for the Advancement of Science.
Webster has also served on a number of not-for-profit boards, most notably Capilano College, Vancouver Aquarium and Marine Science Centre, (President and Chairman), Tynehead Zoological Society, and the President of the Arts, Sciences and Technology Centre (Science World).
He is an honorary member of the Canadian Society of Zoologists and the Soicety of Nematologists (USA) and a fellow of the European Society of Nematologists, the Institute of Biology (UK), the Linnean Society of London (UK), and the Society of Nematologists (USA).
From 2001-2006 he was President and CEO of Welichem BioTech Inc and from 2006 to 2012 he was Chief Scientific Officer.
Professor Webster lives in North Vancouver, BC.
published
Full
Published
The fonds consists of records related to Webster's work as a scientist and administrator at SFU as well as records related to his involvement in a number of external organizations at the local, provincial, and national levels.
The fonds includes correspondence with colleagues and students from around the world, reports, memos and communications with SFU colleagues, and committees, reprints of research articles which he authored, correspondence with contributors to Economic Nematology (the book he edited), and records related to external organizations such as the Arts, Science and Technology Centre of BC, the Science Council of Canada, Natural Sciences and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC), and Tynehead Zoological Society of BC.
The fonds is arranged in 8 series: Senior Administration, Correspondence & Committees, Arts Science and Technology Centre of BC, Science Council of Canada, Tynehead Zoological Society of BC, NSERC, Reprints of Research, Economic Nematology correspondence.
Science and technology; Environment
The records were donated to the Simon Fraser University Archives by John Webster in 5 accessions from 2006 to 2013.
Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Files marked "pending review" must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release and, as a result of the review, access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the reference archivist for more details.
Copyright subsists in all or some of the records. Generally, the university is the copyright owner only to works that the donor authored. Please consult the reference archivist for details about the use of copyrighted materials.
File lists are available.
- Senior Administration, 1967 - 1985; F-222-1; 36 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of records relating to Webster's work as Pro-Tem Dean of Graduate Studies as well as records related to various committees Webster served on at SFU, such as the Resource Allocation Committee, Academic Planning, Salary Committee, Western Vice Presidents meetings, and University Tenure Committee.
  Office of the Vice-President, Academic and Provost; University Tenure Committee
  - Retreat - Faculty / Administration, 1975; F-222-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - small 222-1)
    Textual records
    Pending review
  - Interim dean of graduate studies, 1970; F-222-1-0-0-2 (Archival box - small 222-1)
  - Graduate studies - acting dean - development of faculty of graduate studies, 1970 - 1971; F-222-1-0-0-3 (Archival box - small 222-1)
  - Faculty club committee, 1969 - 1973; F-222-1-0-0-4 (Archival box - small 222-1)
  - Faculty association, 1967 - 1976; F-222-1-0-0-5 (Archival box - small 222-2)
  - Computer assisted instruction programme, 1972 - 1973; F-222-1-0-0-6 (Archival box - small 222-2)
  - Faculty club, 1970; F-222-1-0-0-7 (Archival box - small 222-2)
  - Administration documents - censure, articles, 1967 - 1974; F-222-1-0-0-8 (Archival box - small 222-2)
  - Joint faculty meetings, functional structure, censure, 1968 - 1972; F-222-1-0-0-9 (Archival box - small 222-2)
  - Academic / administrative issues, vol. 2, 1975 - 1981; F-222-1-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 222-3)
  - Academic / administrative issues, vol. 1, 1969 - 1974; F-222-1-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 222-3)
  - Resource allocation committee, 1975 - 1976; F-222-1-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 222-3)
  - President's research grant, 1968 - 1972; F-222-1-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 222-3)
  - Academic planning, 1968 - 1970; F-222-1-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 222-3)
  - Department undergraduate curriculum committee (DUCC), 1968 - 1970; F-222-1-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 222-3)
  - Appraisal of graduate program, University of Guelph, 1982; F-222-1-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 222-3)
  - Defense research board advisory committee on entomological research, 1967; F-222-1-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 222-3)
    Open
  - Salary committee, 1972 - 1973; F-222-1-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 222-3)
  - Western vice-presidents academic (WESTVAC), 1982; F-222-1-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 222-3)
  - Western vice-presidents academic (WESTVAC) 5th Meeting, 1981; F-222-1-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 222-4)
  - National meeting of Vice Presidents, Academic, 1981; F-222-1-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 222-4)
  - Canadian research management association, 1982 - 1985; F-222-1-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 222-4)
  - Canadian association of university research administrators(CAURA), 1985; F-222-1-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 222-4)
  - Royal commission of inquiry into the use of pesticides and herbicides brief by Webster on nematodes, 1973; F-222-1-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 222-4)
  - Crop protection lead committee, 1970; F-222-1-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 222-4)
  - University tenure committee, 1972 - 1973; F-222-1-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 222-4)
  - International development research centre (IDRC) meeting, 1980; F-222-1-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 222-4)
  - Canadian Association of Graduate Schools, 1976 - 1985; F-222-1-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 222-28)
  - Graduate student progress at Simon Fraser University 1974-1980, 1985; F-222-1-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 222-28)
- Correspondence, 1965 - 2002; F-222-2; 1.58 m of textual records
  Series consists of correspondence with colleagues, graduate students, government officials, as well as interdepartmental correspondence. This series primarily consists of correspondence with colleagues regarding research, specimens, equipment, publications and also solicitations from graduate students to study with Webster at SFU. The series is arranged in chronological order.
  - Correspondence, vol. 1, 1965 - 1966; F-222-2-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 222-4)
  - Correspondence, vol. 2, 1965 - 1966; F-222-2-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 222-4)
  - Correspondence, vol. 3, 1965 - 1966; F-222-2-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 222-5)
  - Correspondence, 1966; F-222-2-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 222-5)
  - Correspondence, 1968; F-222-2-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 222-5)
  - Correspondence, 1969 - 1970; F-222-2-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 222-5)
  - Correspondence, 1970; F-222-2-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 222-5)
  - Correspondence, 1972; F-222-2-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 222-6)
  - Correspondence, 1973; F-222-2-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 222-6)
  - Correspondence, 1974; F-222-2-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 222-6)
  - Correspondence, 1975 - 1977; F-222-2-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 222-6)
  - Correspondence, 1977 - 1980; F-222-2-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 222-6)
  - Correspondence, vol. 1, 1970 - 1981; F-222-2-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 222-6)
  - Correspondence, vol. 2, 1970 - 1981; F-222-2-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 222-7)
  - Correspondence, vol. 3, 1970 - 1981; F-222-2-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 222-7)
  - Correspondence, vol. 4, 1970 - 1981; F-222-2-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 222-7)
  - Correspondence, vol. 5, 1970 - 1981; F-222-2-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 222-7)
  - Correspondence, 1978; F-222-2-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 222-7)
  - Correspondence, 1979; F-222-2-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 222-7)
  - Correspondence, 1980; F-222-2-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 222-8)
  - Correspondence, 1981; F-222-2-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 222-8)
  - Correspondence, 1982; F-222-2-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 222-8)
  - Correspondence, 1980 - 1981; F-222-2-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 222-8)
  - Correspondence, 1984; F-222-2-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 222-8)
  - Correspondence, 1984; F-222-2-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 222-9)
  - Correspondence, vol. 1, 1985; F-222-2-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 222-9)
  - Correspondence, vol. 2, 1985; F-222-2-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 222-9)
  - Correspondence, vol. 3, 1985; F-222-2-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 222-9)
  - Correspondence, vol. 4, 1985; F-222-2-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 222-9)
  - Correspondence, vol. 1, 1985 - 1988; F-222-2-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 222-10)
  - Correspondence, vol. 2, 1985 - 1988; F-222-2-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 222-10)
  - Correspondence, vol. 3, 1985 - 1988; F-222-2-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 222-10)
  - Correspondence, vol. 4, 1985 - 1988; F-222-2-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 222-10)
  - Correspondence, vol. 5, 1985 - 1988; F-222-2-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 222-10)
  - Correspondence, vol. 6, 1985 - 1988; F-222-2-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 222-10)
  - Correspondence, vol. 7, 1985 - 1988; F-222-2-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 222-11)
  - Correspondence, vol. 1, 1989 - 1991; F-222-2-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 222-11)
  - Correspondence, vol. 2, 1989 - 1991; F-222-2-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 222-11)
  - Correspondence, vol. 3, 1989 - 1991; F-222-2-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 222-11)
  - Correspondence, vol. 4, 1989 - 1991; F-222-2-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 222-11)
  - Correspondence, vol. 5, 1989 - 1991; F-222-2-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 222-11)
  - Correspondence, vol. 6, 1989 - 1991; F-222-2-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 222-12)
  - Correspondence, vol. 7, 1989 - 1991; F-222-2-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 222-12)
  - Correspondence, vol. 8, 1989 - 1991; F-222-2-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 222-12)
  - Correspondence, vol. 1, 1993 - 1995; F-222-2-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 222-12)
  - Correspondence, vol. 2, 1993 - 1995; F-222-2-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 222-12)
  - Correspondence, vol. 3, 1993 - 1995; F-222-2-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 222-12)
  - Correspondence, vol. 4, 1993 - 1995; F-222-2-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 222-13)
  - Correspondence, vol. 5, 1993 - 1995; F-222-2-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 222-13)
  - Correspondence, vol. 6, 1993 - 1995; F-222-2-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 222-13)
  - Correspondence, vol. 1, 1992 - 1993; F-222-2-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 222-13)
  - Correspondence, vol. 2, 1992 - 1993; F-222-2-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 222-13)
  - Correspondence, vol. 3, 1992 - 1993; F-222-2-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 222-13)
  - Correspondence, vol. 4, 1992 - 1993; F-222-2-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 222-14)
  - Correspondence, vol. 5, 1992 - 1993; F-222-2-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 222-14)
  - Correspondence, vol. 6, 1992 - 1993; F-222-2-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 222-14)
  - Correspondence, vol. 7, 1992 - 1993; F-222-2-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 222-14)
  - Correspondence, vol. 8, 1992 - 1993; F-222-2-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 222-14)
  - Correspondence, 2001 - 2002; F-222-2-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 222-15)
  - Correspondence, 1999 - 2000; F-222-2-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 222-15)
  - Correspondence, 1970 - 1999; F-222-2-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 222-15)
  - Correspondence, 2003 - 2006; F-222-2-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 222-15)
  - Correspondence, 1993 - 2002; F-222-2-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 222-15)
  - Correspondence, 1998; F-222-2-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 222-15)
  - Correspondence, 1998; F-222-2-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 222-16)
  - Correspondence, 1997 - 1998; F-222-2-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 222-16)
  - Correspondence, 1997; F-222-2-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 222-16)
  - Correspondence, 1997; F-222-2-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 222-16)
  - Correspondence, 1997; F-222-2-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 222-16)
  - Correspondence, 1996; F-222-2-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 222-17)
  - Correspondence, 1996; F-222-2-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 222-17)
- Arts, Science and Technology Centre of British Columbia, 1981 - 1984; F-222-3; 29 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to Webster's involvement on the Board of Governors of the Arts, Science and Technology Centre of British Columbia. Series includes correspondence, minutes, agendae, and president's records. Webster was president of the Society from 1980-1981.
  - Arts & Science Technology Centre Society Board of Governors, 1980; F-222-3-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 222-17)
  - Arts & Science Technology Centre Society Board of Governors, 1981 - 1982; F-222-3-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 222-17)
  - Arts & Science Technology Centre Society President's Correspondence, 1980 - 1981; F-222-3-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 222-17)
  - Arts & Science Technology Centre Society President / Past President's Correspondence, vol. 1, 1982 - 1983; F-222-3-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 222-17)
  - Arts & Science Technology Centre Society President / Past President's Correspondence, vol. 2, 1982 - 1983; F-222-3-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 222-18)
  - Arts & Science Technology Centre Society articles and correspondence, 1981; F-222-3-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 222-18)
  - Arts & Science Technology Centre Society nominating committee, 1983; F-222-3-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 222-18)
  - Arts & Science Technology Centre Society minutes, 1983; F-222-3-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 222-18)
  - Arts & Science Technology Centre Society meeting materials, 1983 - 1984; F-222-3-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 222-18)
  - Arts & Science Technology Centre Society general correspondence, 1983 - 1984; F-222-3-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 222-18)
  - Arts & Science Technology Centre Society board of governors meetings, 1985; F-222-3-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 222-18)
  - Arts & Science Technology Centre Society board meeting agendae, and journal articles, 1982 - 1983; F-222-3-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 222-18)
  - Arts & Science Technology Centre Society AGM, 1983 - 1984; F-222-3-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 222-19)
  - Arts & Science Technology Centre Society functional program Boak Alexander, Architects, 1984; F-222-3-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 222-19)
  - Arts & Science Technology Centre Society symposium, 1983; F-222-3-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 222-19)
  - Arts & Science Technology Centre Society guidelines, information, correspondence, 1981; F-222-3-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 222-20)
- Science Council of Canada, 1982 - 1984; F-222-4; 35 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to Webster's involvement on the Science Council of Canada, including records relating to forestry, microtechnolgoy, artificial intelligence and biotechnology. Series includes correspondence, meeting notes, agendae, minutes, and reports.
  - Science Council of Canada, vol. 1, 1982 - 1983; F-222-4-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 222-20)
  - Science Council of Canada, vol. 2, 1982 - 1983; F-222-4-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 222-20)
  - Science Council of Canada meeting Jun 16-17 1983, F-222-4-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 222-20)
  - Science Council of Canada meeting Oct 6-7 1983, F-222-4-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 222-20)
  - Science Council of Canada meeting Dec 15-16 1983, F-222-4-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 222-20)
  - Science Council of Canada biotechnology committee initial input, 1982; F-222-4-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 222-20)
  - Science Council of Canada microtechnology meeting Nov 8 1982, F-222-4-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 222-20)
  - Science Council of Canada artificial intelligence workshop, 1983; F-222-4-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 222-20)
  - Science Council of Canada biotechnology committee minutes, 1983 - 1984; F-222-4-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 222-20)
  - Science Council of Canada regulating the regulators workshop, 1983; F-222-4-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 222-21)
  - Science Council of Canada John Webster's meeting notes, 1982 - 1984; F-222-4-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 222-21)
  - Science Council of Canada statement on the state of forestry, 1982 - 1983; F-222-4-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 222-21)
  - Science Council of Canada forestry report, 1982 - 1984; F-222-4-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 222-21)
  - Science Council of Canada biotechnology committee, vol. 1, 1983 - 1984; F-222-4-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 222-21)
  - Science Council of Canada biotechnology committee, vol. 2, 1983 - 1984; F-222-4-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 222-21)
  - Science Council of Canada biotechnology committee, vol. 3, 1982 - 1983; F-222-4-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 222-21)
  - Science Council of Canada biotechnology committee, vol. 4, 1983; F-222-4-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 222-22)
  - Science Council of Canada biotechnology committee, vol. 5, 1983; F-222-4-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 222-22)
  - Science Council of Canada correspondence, vol. 1, 1984; F-222-4-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 222-22)
  - Science Council of Canada correspondence, vol. 2, 1984; F-222-4-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 222-22)
- Natural Science and Engineering Research Council, 1981 - 1983; F-222-6; 27 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to Webster's participation as chair of the Life Sciences Committee, as well as a member of the Grants and Scholarships Committee, and Joint Selection Committee with SSHRC. Records consists of correspondence, minutes, agenda, reports, meeting notes.
  - Natural Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) ad hoc committee on natural resources, 1982 - 1983; F-222-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 222-23)
  - Natural Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) life sciences GSCS annual reports, 1982 - 1983; F-222-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 222-23)
  - Natural Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) subcommittee on taxonomy, 1982; F-222-6-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 222-23)
  - Natural Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) January 1982 meeting - Ottawa, 1981 - 1982; F-222-6-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 222-23)
  - Natural Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) population biology committee policy meeting, 1981; F-222-6-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 222-23)
  - Natural Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) May-Jun meeting, 1981; F-222-6-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 222-23)
  - Natural Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) grant selection committee membership, 1982; F-222-6-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 222-23)
  - Natural Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) correspondence, 1981 - 1982; F-222-6-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 222-23)
  - Natural Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) John Webster correspondence, 1981 - 1982; F-222-6-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 222-23)
  - Natural Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) general and other correspondence, 1981; F-222-6-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 222-24)
  - Natural Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) allocations task force, 1982 - 1983; F-222-6-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 222-24)
  - Natural Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) population biology, 1982 - 1983; F-222-6-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 222-24)
  - Natural Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) psychology, 1983; F-222-6-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 222-24)
  - Natural Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) animal biology, 1982 - 1983; F-222-6-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 222-24)
  - Natural Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) plant biology, 1982 - 1983; F-222-6-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 222-24)
  - Natural Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) cell biology, 1982 - 1983; F-222-6-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 222-24)
  - Natural Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) grants and scholarship committee meeting Nov 1981, F-222-6-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 222-24)
  - Natural Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) forestry, 1981 - 1982; F-222-6-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 222-24)
  - Natural Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) correspondence, 1982 - 1983; F-222-6-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 222-25)
- Tynehead Zoological Society of BC, 1983 - 1986; F-222-5; 7 cm of textual records